(upbeat rock music)
♪ Once upon a time not so long ago ♪
♪ Tommy used to work on the docks ♪
♪ Union's been on strike,
he's down on his luck ♪
♪ It's tough, so tough ♪
♪ Gina works the diner all day ♪
♪ Working for her man ♪
♪ She brings home her
pay for love, for love ♪
♪ She says we've got to
hold on to what we've got ♪
♪ It doesn't make a difference
if we make it or not ♪
♪ We've got each other and that's a lot ♪
♪ For love, we'll give it a shot ♪
♪ Whoa, we're halfway there ♪
♪ Whoa, livin' on a prayer ♪
♪ Take my hand, we'll make it I swear ♪
♪ Tommy's got his six-string in hock ♪
♪ Now he's holding in what
he used to make it talk ♪
♪ So tough, it's tough ♪
♪ Gina dreams of running away ♪
♪ When she cries in the night ♪
♪ Tommy whispers, baby,
it's okay someday ♪
♪ We've got to hold on to what we've got ♪
♪ It doesn't make a difference
if we make it or not ♪
♪ We've got each other and that's a lot ♪
♪ For love, we'll give it a shot ♪
♪ Whoa, we're halfway there ♪
♪ Whoa, livin' on a prayer ♪
♪ Take my hand, we'll make it I swear ♪
♪ Livin' on a prayer ♪
♪ Oh, we've got to hold on, ready or not ♪
♪ You live for the fight when
that's all that you got ♪
♪ Whoa, we're halfway there ♪
♪ Whoa, livin' on a prayer ♪
♪ Take my hand, we'll make it I swear ♪
♪ Whoa, we're halfway there ♪
♪ Whoa, livin' on a prayer ♪
♪ Take my hand, we'll make it I swear ♪
♪ Whoa, we're halfway there ♪
♪ Whoa, livin' on a prayer ♪
♪ Take my hand, we'll make it I swear ♪